This summer, World Cup came to
Miami.
Office cups, school leagues,
and even hackathon fellows.
and they still
use a piece of paper to
track all the results.
That's what inspired us to create
a solution
to convert it all into a
beautiful league management software.
Let's take a look.
Pick it from a library
or do it live.
Gemini reads the photo.
A second AI pass checks the
extraction.
Review the teams and scores before
publishing.
Look at this.
Panthers versus Shellhacks.
It knows that this is a
group stage,
shows the standings,
and we could read it out.
Standings after two games.
First, Panthers, three points.
Second, Organizers, one point.
Third, Wizards, one point.
Fourth, Shellhacks, zero points.
Here we go.
The games,
the bracket,
With the handwriting or typing,
convert it into beautiful
statistics
New result?
Add another photo and review what
changed.
Snap to League, built at ShellHacks
on the existing EasyChamp platform.